bassettfurniture.com 2009-04-15

# Bassett Furniture » Customer Service

Welcome to [www.bassettfurniture.com](http://www.bassettfurniture.com/).  Please take a few minutes to review our Privacy Statement for this site.

This Statement of Privacy applies only to the website of Bassett Furniture Industries (Bassett), located on the internet at [www.bassettfurniture.com](http://www.bassettfurniture.com/) and governs data collection and usage. By using the Bassett website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

This is the website of Bassett Furniture Industries.

Our postal address is:  
Bassett Furniture Industries  
3525 Fairystone Park Hwy.  
Bassett, VA 24055

Email address: [support@bassettfurniture.com](mailto:support@bassettfurniture.com)  
Telephones:  276.629.6000

_Information We Collect_  
For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes a visitors domain name, IP address, browser type, access times and referring website addresses.  We also collect and store any information provided to us via forms or emails.

Bassett collects and uses information to operate the Bassett Furniture Industries website and deliver the services you have requested.  Any information provided to us via this site, including emails, can be used by Bassett for research, analysis, and internal statistics.

From time to time, we may also use this information to contact you in regards to a question that you have asked, or to inform you of new product or services.  We may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services.  If you do not wish to receive emails or mailings from us, you may request this at the above address.

Occasionally we exchange our customer lists with other reputable companies.  If you do not wish to receive mailings from these companies, or if you no longer wish to receive our catalogs, please send us your name and address as it appears on the mailing label on your catalog to the email or postal addresses above.  Please note that any requests to remove or update your personal information may take up to ten days for your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request.

 _  
With Respect to Cookies_

We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site.

_With Respect to Personal Information_  
If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address, writing to us at the above address. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address or contacting us via telephone.

_Security of Information_  
Bassett has the appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.  We secure all personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Bassett secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
